const data = [
    {
        question: 'small',
        options: ['slight','learn','obtain','start','communicate','choose'],
        answer: '0'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'study',
        options: ['slight','learn','obtain','start','communicate','choose'],
        answer: '1'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'get',
        options: ['slight','learn','obtain','start','communicate','choose'],
        answer: '2'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'begin',
        options: ['slight','learn','obtain','start','communicate','choose'],
        answer: '3'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'speak',
        options: ['slight','learn','obtain','start','communicate','choose'],
        answer: '4'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'pick',
        options: ['slight','learn','obtain','start','communicate','choose'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        question: 'to discover or perceive after consideration is to ',
        options: ['find','boost','increase','gather','assemble'],
        answer: '0'
    },
    {
        question: 'to bring together into one group, collection, or place is to ',
        options: ['find','boost','increase','gather','assemble'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'to put or fit together; put together the parts of is to ',
        options:  ['find','boost','increase','gather','assemble'],
        answer: '4'
    },
    {
        question: 'to make greater, as in number, size, strength, or quality; augment; add to is to',
        options:  ['find','boost','increase','gather','assemble'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'to increase; raise or to',
        options: ['find','boost','increase','gather','assemble'],
        answer: '1'
    },
    {
        question: 'The paper  ____  was followed by a reform of the metallic currency.',
        options: ['spit','easy','currency','shortage','wild'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'A  ____  of teachers has put thousands of students in overcrowded classrooms.',
        options: ['spit','easy','currency','shortage','wild'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: '____ cats roamed around the gas station',
        options: ['spit','easy','currency','shortage','wild'],
        answer: '4'
    },
    {
        question: 'This isn’t  ____  for you, is it?',
        options:['spit','easy','currency','shortage','wild'],
        answer: '1'
    },
    {
        question: 'The young man’s  ____  flew through the air and hit the pavement.',
        options: ['spit','easy','currency','shortage','wild'],
        answer: '0'
    },
    {
        question: 'calf',
        options: ['wonderful','urge','silly','baby cow','courageous'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'amazing',
        options: ['wonderful','urge','silly','baby cow','courageous'],
        answer: '0'
    },
    {
        question: 'brave',
        options: ['wonderful','urge','silly','baby cow','courageous'],
        answer: '4'
    },
    {
        question: 'funny',
        options: ['wonderful','urge','silly','baby cow','courageous'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'hurry',
        options: ['wonderful','urge','silly','baby cow','courageous'],
        answer: '1'
    },
    {
        question: 'black',
        options: ['and soul','dog','English','review','hole'],
        answer: '4'
    },
    {
        question: 'book',
        options: ['and soul','dog','English','review','hole'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'heart',
        options: ['and soul','dog','English','review','hole'],
        answer: '0'
    },
    {
        question: 'old',
        options: ['and soul','dog','English','review','hole'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'police',
        options:['and soul','dog','English','review','hole'],
        answer: '1'
    },
    {
        question: 'big',
        options: ['go','begin','plan','listen','large'],
        answer: '4'
    },
    {
        question: 'study',
        options: ['go','read','plan','listen','large'],
        answer: '1'
    },
    {
        question: 'receive',
        options: ['go','begin','plan','get','large'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'talk',
        options: ['go','begin','plan','get','large','speak'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        question: 'To cover with paper or material is to',
        options: ['attend','assemble','approach','arrive','admit','announce','arrange','adjust','accept','wrap'],
        answer: '9'
    },
    {
        question: 'To state or make public is to',
        options: ['attend','assemble','approach','arrive','admit','announce','arrange','adjust','accept','wrap'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        question: 'To get somewhere is to',
        options: ['attend','assemble','approach','arrive','admit','announce','arrange','adjust','accept','wrap'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'To put something together is to',
        options: ['attend','assemble','approach','arrive','admit','announce','arrange','adjust','accept','wrap'],
        answer: '1'
    },
    {
        question: 'More and more people go  ____  for their holidays these days.',
        options: ['awkward','ancient','ahead','adequate','articulate','alert','accurate','abroad','adult','agressive'],
        answer: '7'
    },
    {
        question: 'Drivers need to remain  ____  when in charge of a car.',
        options: ['awkward','ancient','ahead','adequate','articulate','alert','accurate','abroad','adult','agressive'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        question: 'The city has many  ____  and interesting buildings.',
        options:['awkward','ancient','ahead','adequate','articulate','alert','accurate','abroad','adult','agressive'],
        answer: '1'
    },
    {
        question: 'She´s a highly  ____  person who explains things clearly.',
        options: ['awkward','ancient','ahead','adequate','articulate','alert','accurate','abroad','adult','agressive'],
        answer: '4'
    },
    {
        question: 'He´s a very  ____  person - always getting into fights.',
        options: ['awkward','ancient','ahead','adequate','articulate','alert','accurate','abroad','adult','agressive'],
        answer: '9'
    },
    {
        question: 'timetable',
        options: ['line','joint','command','prize','mess','fright','schedule','dock','stage','mistake'],
        answer: '6'
    },
    {
        question: 'reward',
        options: ['line','joint','command','prize','mess','fright','schedule','dock','stage','mistake'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'queue',
        options: ['line','joint','command','prize','mess','fright','schedule','dock','stage','mistake'],
        answer: '0'
    },
    {
        question: 'phase',
        options: ['line','joint','command','prize','mess','fright','schedule','dock','stage','mistake'],
        answer: '8'
    },
    {
        question: 'error',
        options: ['line','joint','command','prize','mess','fright','schedule','dock','stage','mistake'],
        answer: '9'
    },
    {
        question: 'big + ',
        options: ['bomb','audition','scissors','rod','classes','strings','salesman','seep','minister','seat','house'],
        answer: '10'
    },
    {
        question: 'aerobics + ',
        options: ['bomb','audition','scissors','rod','classes','strings','salesman','seep','minister','seat','house'],
        answer: '4'
    },
    {
        question: 'agriculture + ',
        options: ['bomb','audition','scissors','rod','classes','strings','salesman','seep','minister','seat','house'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'aisle + ',
        options: ['bomb','audition','scissors','rod','classes','strings','salesman','seep','minister','seat','house'],
        answer: '9'
    },
    {
        question: 'apron + ',
        options: ['bomb','audition','scissors','rod','classes','strings','salesman','seep','minister','seat','house'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        question: 'atom + ',
        options: ['bomb','audition','scissors','rod','classes','strings','salesman','seep','minister','seat','house'],
        answer: '0'
    }/* ,
    {
        question: '',
        options: ['','','','',''],
        answer: ''
    } */
]

export default data;